ochospace.com 2014-03-07

# Ocho Space|Everyone's Playing.

**Effective as of December 10, 2007**

This Statement of Privacy Principles describes the policies and procedures of TYLER Projects for the collection, use, and dissemination of personally identifiable information about our consumers in both the online and offline world.

This Policy applies to all web sites and services owned or provided by TYLER Projects, including its subsidiaries (collectively "TYLER Websites"). TYLER Websites include, but are not limited to, [Ochospace.com](http://ochospace.com/), [Mobileweapon.net](http://mobileweapon.net/), [Tylerprojects.com](http://tylerprojects.com/), [Tylerproject.com](http://tylerproject.com/), [Chocopets.com](http://chocopets.com/) as well as other TYLER-branded services. New sites, domain names, or services that we add to the TYLER Websites will be subject to this Policy.

The TYLER Websites are general audience web sites, and TYLER Projects does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age.

From time to time we may revise this Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our information collection and use practices, the features of the TYLER Websites, or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If we materially change our practices regarding use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.  

**COLLECTION: Collection of PII by TYLER Projects**

**General.** TYLER Projects collects PII in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in certain activities including (i) registration for certain online services and tools such as downloads, message boards, chat rooms or other community services; (ii) registration for special communications, such as email updates and newsletters; (iii) subscription registration; (iv) purchase products or services from or through the TYLER Websites; (v) user surveys; (vi) events, sweepstakes, contests or promotions; and (vii) registration for online multi- or single-player gaming. We may obtain PII from third parties that we consider to be reputable. We also may receive on the TYLER Websites user-generated content or information of any type or medium, which may include PII, including but not limited to: text chat and video images from forums; user game reviews; and Flash game submissions.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in public areas of an TYLER Projects Site, such as the member home pages and message boards, your information can be viewed and possibly used by others. We advise users to be especially careful in such public areas about disclosing PII, such as full name, home address, or phone number.

**Cookies.** Cookies are small bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit the TYLER Websites. We may use cookies to recognize users who have already registered for an TYLER Projects Site, allowing those users to speed up their future activities on the TYLER Websites. Information about your activities on TYLER Websites and other non-personally identifiable information about you may also be used to tailor the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests. 

Third party advertisements displayed on the TYLER Websites may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers. TYLER Projects does not control these cookies. You should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the "Notice" section below for more information on third party advertisements.

TYLER Projects may use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of the TYLER Websites to PII obtained from you or a third party. For example, if you've asked us to provide you with information about our products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on the TYLER Websites may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. We will not coordinate your PII and web site activity information in this manner without first obtaining your express affirmative consent. 

You can set your computer to alert you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies, you may not have access to certain features on the TYLER Websites.

**Web beacons.** The TYLER Websites may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that may be used to assist in delivering or accessing cookies on our sites and allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

We may also employ Web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics and determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. We prohibit Web beacons on our sites from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.

Finally, we may work with other companies that advertise on the TYLER Websites to place Web beacons on their sites in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement on an TYLER Projects site results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser's site.

**NOTICE: TYLER Projects Will Provide You with Notice About its PII Collection Practices**

When you voluntarily provide PII in response to our request or we authorize a third party to collect PII from you on the TYLER Websites, we will inform you about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected, and the types of uses TYLER Projects will make of the information At the time you provide your PII, TYLER Projects will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII (See "Choice" below). This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and with whom we may want to share your personal information, as provided in this Policy (See "Use" below).

When you sign up with our partners for services such as game hosting, userpages, and other services, you are providing information to the partner offering the service as well as to TYLER Projects. Use of your PII by the partner is subject to that partner's privacy policy, and you should carefully read the privacy policy of the partner providing the service before deciding to take advantage of the service.

The TYLER Websites may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with an TYLER Projects or affiliated entity's logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by TYLER Projects. The TYLER Websites also carry advertisements from other companies. TYLER Projects is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to the TYLER Websites or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you've left an TYLER Projects Site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you.

**Third Party Advertising.  
**Some ads appearing on this website are delivered to you by Videoegg Network and Lookery, our Web advertising partners. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. For more information about online advertising, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please visit _[www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)_. **Registration Forms and Surveys.**  
Usage of out site or participation in our Opt-in surveys requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email address), unique identifiers (like their email address), and demographic information (such as their zip code or age). Contact information from these forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers (such as email address) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity, and for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

**Contests.**  
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information. This information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out section below. **External Links.**  
This site contains links to other sites. TYLER Projects is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

CHILDREN'S GUIDELINES: This site meets the Online Privacy Protection Act guidelines.

**CHOICE: TYLER Projects Will Provide You with Choices About the Use of Your PII**

TYLER Projects will not use your PII for purposes different from those about which you have been notified, or share your PII with third parties that are not affiliated with TYLER Projects, unless you have asked to receive certain information and/or services from third parties or participate in certain third-party programs (such as demos or subscriptions) and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your PII or you have consented to such sharing.

OPT-OUT: Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us. Email: account@mobileweapon.net

**USE: TYLER Projects's Use of PII**

TYLER Projects will use your PII in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If TYLER Projects obtains PII from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy. TYLER Projects may use PII in aggregate, anonymous form for research purposes.

We may contact you regarding account status, changes to this Policy, our User Agreement or other terms of use, to confirm your registration, for customer service purposes or for any other business reason related to your use of TYLER Websites.

Provided you have given us consent, TYLER Projects may also share your PII with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with TYLER Projects, but would like to send you information about their products and services, such as sponsors of promotions that appear on the TYLER Websites. We will never share your credit card information with third parties except those TYLER Projects uses to perform tasks (such as order fulfillment and payment processing) required to complete purchases you make through web sites.

TYLER Projects employees, agents, and contractors are required to have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII. TYLER Projects may share your PII with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (i.e., order fulfillment, statistical analyses), but they must have agreed only to use your PII to provide TYLER Projects with a specific service and not for any other purpose.

TYLER Projects may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows TYLER Projects to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the TYLER Websites. Your non-PII and click stream data about your activities on our sites may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. These companies have agreed not to share your information with any third party or use it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with TYLER Projects's advertisers and business partners.

TYLER Projects automatically updates software used in conjunction with certain of the services available on the TYLER Websites. In order to accomplish this, TYLER Projects collects information about a user's current version of the software from the user's computer. This information is not archived but is only used to determine which software requires updating.

TYLER Projects may copy text chat or video images from chat rooms on the TYLER Websites and may use and therefore disclose such material for use in connection with promoting the TYLER Websites. In addition, TYLER Projects may collect other user-generated content such as user reviews and Flash game submissions to post on our community site, [Mobileweapon.net](http://mobileweapon.net/).

There may be instances when TYLER Projects may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of TYLER Projects, to protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites; to investigate, prevent or protect against suspected fraud, illegal activity, violations of our user agreement or for risk management purposes; or to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. In addition, if TYLER Projects sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, TYLER Projects may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction.

**SECURITY: TYLER Projects Protects the Security of PII**

TYLER Projects uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification. Passwords and other sensitive information stored by TYLER Projects are encrypted in transit.

Notwithstanding these security measures, please be aware that when you submit PII to the TYLER Websites over the Internet, the information may travel over many systems that are not under the TYLER Projects's control and may not be secure.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. Anyone who has access to your password will have access to your PII, as well as to any credit card information that you have submitted. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

**ACCESS: How to Access, Correct, or Delete Your Preferences Regarding Your PII**

To access, correct or update your account or other Personal Information such as your city or interests, please use the "My Account" link on the TYLER Projects Site on which you are registered.

If you want to update your email address or stop receiving these types of promotional emails, please follow the procedures to unsubscribe at the bottom of any email we send you.

**REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: How to Contact TYLER Projects About Privacy Concerns**

If you have any other questions, comments or complaints about this Policy, please email us at [_support@tylerproject.com_](mailto:support@tylerproject.com).
